{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was...",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Victor Solomon.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Thunderstorm Artis.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Kennedy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Johnson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Johnson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Kennedy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Caleb Johnson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Ch√©",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Canaan James Hill",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Caleb Johnson.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kolbi Jordan",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Kolbi Jordan.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Kolbi Jordan.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Thunderstorm Artis.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Canaan James Hill.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 6
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Jordin Sparks",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Carrie Underwood.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Kris Allen",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Phillip Phillips.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year is Candice Glover.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Laine Hardy.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The winner of American Idol this year was Jordin Sparks.",
      "needle": "This year's American Idol is still ongoing, and the final results have not been announced yet.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "Who was the winner of American Idol this year?",
      "frequency": 9
    }
  ]
}